{
    "subject": "resource/Pfizer_UK",
    "predicate": "ontology/product",
    "object": "resource/Pharmaceutical_drug",
    "human_readable": "Pfizer UK produces a Pharmaceutical drug.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.950485110282898,
            "question": "Is Pfizer UK involved in the pharmaceutical industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.872997522354126,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a drug produced by Pfizer UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8496964573860168,
            "question": "What is the role of research and development in the production of pharmaceutical drugs by Pfizer UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8394381403923035,
            "question": "What does Pfizer UK produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8039592504501343,
            "question": "Are there any other companies besides Pfizer UK that produce pharmaceuticals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6722075939178467,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges faced by pharmaceutical companies like Pfizer UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5961757898330688,
            "question": "What kind of product does Pfizer UK manufacture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36952972412109375,
            "question": "Where is Pfizer UK located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3039819598197937,
            "question": "What is the main function of a pharmaceutical drug?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2063755840063095,
            "question": "How do pharmaceutical drugs benefit society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pfizer UK produces a Pharmaceutical drug.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8017_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main function of a pharmaceutical drug?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8017_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Pfizer UK located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8017_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of product does Pfizer UK manufacture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8017_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8017_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why:\n\n* The documents consistently mention Pfizer's presence and activities in the UK, including production of medicines for the NHS and its role in R&D collaborations.  \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Pfizer's presence and activities in the UK, including its history of producing pharmaceutical drugs. For example, one document states, \"Since our first UK facility opened its doors in 1952, we have remained committed to discovering and developing new and innovative ways to prevent and treat disease,\" which supports the triple that Pfizer UK produces a Pharmaceutical drug."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}